{
    "subject": "resource/Philip_Emeagwali",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Emeagwali, Philip",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Philip Emeagwali is Emeagwali, Philip.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9870339632034302,
            "question": "What is the full name of Philip Emeagwali?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9694376587867737,
            "question": "What is Philip Emeagwali's given name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9681062698364258,
            "question": "What is Philip Emeagwali's surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9653255939483643,
            "question": "Is 'Emeagwali' Philip's given name or surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9641528725624084,
            "question": "What is the middle name of Philip Emeagwali?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9397602081298828,
            "question": "Does Philip Emeagwali have a middle name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9392755627632141,
            "question": "Is Philip Emeagwali's first name spelled 'Philip' or 'Phillipe'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9045355319976807,
            "question": "What is the correct order of Philip Emeagwali's names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8344894647598267,
            "question": "How is Philip Emeagwali's first and last name arranged?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8160802721977234,
            "question": "If you were to introduce Philip Emeagwali, what order would you use his names in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Philip Emeagwali is Emeagwali, Philip.",
            "html": "dbpedia_613_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Philip Emeagwali's first and last name arranged?",
            "html": "dbpedia_613_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the correct order of Philip Emeagwali's names?",
            "html": "dbpedia_613_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Philip Emeagwali's first name spelled 'Philip' or 'Phillipe'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_613_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_613_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_613_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_613_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_613_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_613_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_613_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_613_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_613_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_613_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_613_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response in the requested JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention Philip Emeagwali as a person with several credentials and achievements, but there is no information to suggest that his full name is simply \"Emeagwali, Philip.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information about Philip Emeagwali's full name as \"Philip Chukwurah Emeagwali,\" which supports the statement that his full name is \"Emeagwali, Philip.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The context information does not provide the given name for Philip Emeagwali. The only name provided for him is his surname, Emeagwali, but there is no indication of a first name or a full name in the given context.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several sources clearly state his full name as Philip Emeagwali.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The first piece of context information (1) lists his full name as \"Philip Emeagwali\" which is consistent with the subsequent pieces of context information that also list his full name as \"Philip Emeagwali\".",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}